好，现在该你动手了
All right.
Now it's your turn.
在CursorLoader和ForecastAdapter中使用projection
Use a projection in your implementation
of the CursorLoader and ForecastAdapter
来让代码更有效率
to make your code a bit more efficient
in its use of the content provider and
database.
在ForecastAdapter里面
In the ForecastAdapter,
你要修改convertCursorRowToUXFormat()函数
you'll be modifying the convert
cursor row to UX format function.
因为我们之后的教学要用到这个projection
Because our code will be making use of
this projection in future sessions,
所以我们已经为你做好了第一步和第二步
we've done step one and
step two for you.
查看下面的笔记
See the instructor notes for
the string array you should use for
把它们用在你的代码中
our projection and the constants for
the column indices.
注意，比起现在UI中用到的数据，我们获取了更多点的数据
Note that we get more data than
we are using in the UI right now.